护士:卢克布鲁沃尔,你可以去见医生了.
Nurse: Luke Power, the doctor will see you now.
卢克:她病的更重,让她先去.
Luke: She looks sick, take her.
杰森:请等一下.你没有什么好怕的.
Jason: Give us just a second.There is no reason to be scared.
卢克:哦,是的,
Luke: Oh yeah the last time I saw a doctor you went poking around like
上次看病的时候,那个医生像是土耳其的缉毒警官,板着脸对我指手画脚的.
a Turkish drug enforcement officer with an attitude.
杰森:相信我,孩子,医生是你特殊的朋友.
Jason: Trust me pal, the doctor is your very special friend.
斯洛瓦基安医生:过来吧,勇敢点,
Doctor Slovakian: Let's go champ, don't worry;
别担心.午饭后,我还没死去一个饿病人呢.
I haven't lost a patient since lunch.
杰森:他在逗你呢,他逗你呢.医生开玩笑呢.
Jason: He's kidding, he's kidding, the doctor's kidding.
去吧,嘿,嘿,
There you go, hey, hey.
他好几年没看医生了,所以有点担心…哇,
See, he hasn't seen a doctor for years that's why he is so...like you care.
怎么搞的像尼克松要辞职似的呢.
Wow, looks like Nixon's gonna resign.
卢克:好好看着你的手,骗子.
Luke: Keep your hands to yourself you quack.
杰森:没问题的,一切尽在掌握.
Jason: No problem, everything's under control.
斯洛瓦基安医生:放松点,小伙子.
Doctor Slovakian: Take it easy Ace.
杰森:嘿,怎么了?
Jason: Hey what's going on?
卢克:我这位特殊的朋友刚才想用冰棒棍儿憋死我.
Luke: My very special friend just tried to choke me with a Popsicle stick.
斯洛瓦基安医生:这是很常规的检查,他想咬我.
Doctor Slovakian: It's a very normal examination, he tried to bite me.
给我坐好,小子,要不我叫兽医来了.
You settle down scooter or I'll have to call a Vet.
杰森:嘿,嘿,
Jason: Hey, hey Luke,
卢克,你看,检查没什么的.
just so you can see an examination doesn't have to hurt,
我让斯洛瓦基安医生给我做同样的检查,好吗?
I'm gonna Doctor Slovakian do to me exactly what he would do to you ok...
斯洛瓦基安医生:好的,解开你的衬衣.
Doctor Slovakian: Fine, unbutton your shirt sport.
就这样,呼吸放松,呼吸放松.
Whoops, got your nose, got your nose.
杰森:你看,卢克,这没什么.小菜一碟,
Jason: See Luke, I don't feel a thing, it's a piece of cake, easy as pie,
太简单了.一切都很顺利.哎吆…这并不疼,
everything's under contr...ouch.That wasn't a hurt ouch,
只是有点痒.哎吆,因为感觉很舒服,哎吆,
it was just a tickled, ouch, because it felt so darn good, ouch,
就像挠痒痒呢.哎吆,别戳我了,别戳我的鼻子了.
like those giants uh, ouch, quit poking me and stop taking off my nose.
本:那么,疝气是怎么回事?
Ben: What is a hernia anyway?
麦琪:本,在饭桌上别谈这样的事.
Maggie: Ben it's not something you want to talk about at the dinner table.
迈克:就是说,爸爸的肚子鼓起来了.
Mike: Basically dad's guts are popping out.
卢克:医生一摸他的肚子,他就受不了了.是巧合吗?我不觉得.
Luke: It was fine until the doctor started poking at it, coincidence, I think not.
杰森:哦,麦琪,
Jason: Awe, Maggie you're serving honey glazed chicken,
你做了蜂蜜鸡.知道我不能吃东西,你还做蜂蜜鸡.
I can't eat a thing and you're serving honey glazed chicken.
麦琪:哦,我做饭的时候还不知道你明天要做手术.
Maggie: Oh, when I started cooking I didn't know you were going to have
那我怎么办,给他们上剩菜吗?
surgery tomorrow, what do you want me to do, serve them moldy left overs?
杰森:那也不错啊.
Jason: That would be nice.
克莉丝:吃我的吧,爸爸.我想吃花生奶油三明治.
Chrissy: Thinking of mine Daddy, I want a peanut butter sandwich.
麦琪:克莉丝,你早饭和午饭吃的就是花生奶油三明治.
Maggie: Chrissy you had a peanut butter sandwich for breakfast and lunch today.
克莉丝:有好吃的那还不吃个够啊.
Chrissy: When you find a winner, stick with it.
麦琪:我没时间跟你拌嘴.开萝尔,给她做花生奶油三明治.
Maggie: I don't have time to fight with you.Carol, make her a peanut butter sandwich.
开萝尔:但是,妈妈,她就像个惯坏的公主,你得讲原则.
Carol: But Mom she's acting like a spoiled kid, you need to take a stand.
麦琪:好的,给她做三明治,要不都出去.
Maggie: Ok, make her the sandwich but get out of my house.
杰森:为什么?为什么呢?
Jason: Why me?Why now?
迈克:爸爸,没什么,别担心,妈妈会改日给你做蜂蜜鸡的.
Mike: Dad it's alright, don't worry mom can make this chicken dinner another time.
杰森:别提鸡了;精神病学会要在周日举办年度"黑领带"宴会.
Jason: Forget the chicken;
Sunday is The Annual Psychiatric Association Black Tie Banquet.
迈克:哦哦…你肯定错过了,爸爸.
Mike: Woo hoo, sure lucky you're missing this one Dad.
杰森:我肯定不会错过的,这次由我操办.
Jason: I wouldn't miss it for the world Mike, I'm organizing it.
麦琪:哦,你不能这样.医生说你你可参加宴会,但得让别人来组织.
Maggie: Oh, no you don't, the doctor said you could go to the banquet but you have to get someone else to organize it.
杰森:呃,作为活动的组织者,
Jason: Uh uh, as event coordinator I get to introduce the guest of honor,
我还要介绍贵宾呢,他恰恰是我一生中最重要的人物.
who happens to be only one of the most important men in my life.
迈克:维迪尔萨逊?
Mike: Videl Sassoon?
杰森:不,是阿尔佛里德比罗斯医生,我的心理学教授.他折磨过我,
Jason: No, Doctor Alfred Bellows, my psychology professor, he tormented me,
恐吓过我,让我自惭形愧.他对我就像是父亲.
he browbeated me, made me feel like dirt, he was like a father to me.
开萝尔:但你最后却给他颁奖.这太有戏剧性了.
Carol: And you finally get to honor him, that's really beautiful.
迈克:哦,让我说一句,
Mike: Oh, give me a break Carol;
开萝尔.如果让我介绍我的那些顽固的教授,我连个屁也不放一个.
if I got to introduce one of my nut bar professors I certainly wouldn't
对不起,爸爸.
bust a gut over it.Sorry Dad.
开萝尔:这很正常,迈克.
Carol: Common Mike, you're an actor,
你是个演员,如果有机会介绍安东尼霍普金斯,你会吗?
what if you got the chance to introduce Anthony Hopkins at a dinner?
迈克:谁?
Mike: Who?
开萝尔:好吧,斯格特贝尔.
Carol: Ok, Scott Bail.
迈克:我,介绍查尔斯先生?哇.
Mike: Me, introduce Mister Charles in charge himself, wow.
迈克:嘿,爸爸.
Mike: Hey Dad.
杰森:嘿,迈克.我住院期间,有件事需要你为我做一下.
Jason: Hey Mike, I got something I need you to do for me while I'm in the hospital.
迈克:好的,爸爸,
Mike: OK, well don't worry about a thing Dad;
你尽管放心好了.你不在的时候,我会每天至少痛扁本一次的.
while you're gone I'll smack Ben around at least once a day.
杰森:不是这个,是周日的宴会.你看,我病了,你得帮我办件大事.
Jason: No, It's about the banquet on Sunday, you see with me sick, I got a big job for you.
迈克:哦,嘿,放心吧.我会把一切都推掉.
Mike: Oh hey, rest easy; I'll cancel the whole thing.
杰森:实际上,我是希望你保证把一切都安排妥当的.
Jason: Actually I was kinda hoping you'd make sure that everything got set up.
迈克:哦,爸爸,是这样的.学期过半了,我打算干几个通宵把功课都好好地复习一下.
Mike: Ah gee Dad, I don't know, it's mid-terms and I'm gonna be pulling
all-niters as it is just to figure out how to get out of them
杰森:算了吧.我有几个电话号码.酒店的餐饮部经理负责装饰场地.
Jason: Come on, I got some phone numbers here, the hotel catering manager, the guy who does the decorations,
还有一个是负责音乐四重奏的.我可以拜托给你吗?
that agent whose in charge of the string quartet, now can I count on you?
迈克:爸爸,你了解我的.
Mike: Dad you know me.
杰森:是的,可以交给你吗?
Jason: Yes, can I count on you?
迈克:好的,我想我可以,可…
Mike: Well, I guess I could but...
杰森:谢谢;你知道宴会对我很重要.谢谢.
Jason: Thanks; hey that banquet means a lot to me, thanks.
迈克:(吹口哨)本,卢克,快过来.
Mike: (whistling sound) Ben, Luke, get down here.
本:嘿,怎么了?
Ben: Hey what's up?
迈克:伙计们,
Mike: Well guys, am,
爸爸要住院,他交给我一个重要的任务.
with Dad gone to the hospital he's got a big job for me and you guys
你俩要替我来完成.
are gonna do it.
杰森:什么破床啊.我也讨厌这些枕头.太差了,哦,什么烂托盘.
Jason: Stupid bed.I hate these pillows too, they're just stupid, ah, stupid tray.
麦琪:亲爱的,你好像有点烦躁.
Maggie: Honey you seem a little anxious.
杰森:我不烦躁,
Jason: I'm not anxious Maggie;
麦琪;如果烦躁,
if I was anxious I would be complaining about every little thing.
我会对每件小事都发牢骚的.
Carol must u breathe through your mouth.
卢克:你说过,这么没什么好怕的,
Luke: You know, there's no reason to be scared,
医生你是特殊的朋友.
the doctor is your very special friend.
杰森:我说卢克,我确实相信你已经融入这个家庭了,因为你开始嘲笑我了.
Jason: You know Luke, I really believe you are becoming part of the family, cause you're starting to tick me off.
迈克:这提醒了我,本到哪去了?
Mike: Which reminds me, where is Ben?
麦琪:哦,迈克,别喊了.
Maggie: Oh Mike, stop that, your brother is very sensitive;
你弟弟很敏感;他也许躲一边去了,这样,就不会让我们看到他难过的样子了.
he's probably wandered off so we wouldn't see how upset he is.
本:太谢谢你了,护士.我现在能洗海棉擦身澡了.
Ben: Thank you so much nurse, I think I'll have my sponge bath now.
开萝尔:我记得上次我住院还是做扁桃体手术的时候.
Carol: I remember the last time I was in a hospital was when I had my
那个医生给我打麻药的时候说:
tonsils out, when the doctor gave me the ether he said,
"你是我见过的最漂亮的小姑娘".
"You're the prettiest little girl I've ever seen."
迈克:开萝尔,你当时发生幻觉了吧.
Mike: Carol you were clearly hallucinating.
怀特萨德医生:嘿,我是怀特萨德医生.我负责你的手术.
Doctor Whiteside: Hi I'm Doctor Whiteside, I'll be doing the surgery.
麦琪:哦,嘿.
Maggie: Oh hi.
怀特萨德医生:我来告诉你们这只是个很普通的小手术,我不想让你们过分紧张.
Doctor Whiteside: I want you to know the procedure's fairly routine so I don't expect any complication.
杰森:对不起,还记得我吗?喂,这就是来这里的原因.
Jason: Excuse me, remember me, hello, the reason we're here.
怀特萨德医生:哦,抱歉,我要给你打一针.
Doctor Whiteside: Oh excuse me I need to administer this.
杰森:是我,是我,你得跟我说说,我,我,我,我,我…
Jason: Me, me you can talk to me you know, me, me, me, me, me...
怀特萨德医生:喂,西沃医生.今天感觉怎么样?
Doctor Whiteside: Hello Doctor Sever, How are we feeling today?
杰森:哦,感觉还好,
Jason: Oh we are feeling just fine thank you Doctor,
谢谢你医生.只是我们浪费了45分钟在楼下填了一大堆烂表格,
except we wasted 45 minutes just filling out a bunch of dumb forms downstairs
然后就是坐在这间冷的像冰球馆一样的房间里,
and then we sat in a little paper napkin with our cheeks to the wind,
冻的脸颊发硬.除此之外,
in a room the temperature of a hockey ring thank you,
我们还是很开心的,就像…
other than that we are just as happy as a.....
蛤蜊…灰熊…小鱼…青蛙…兔子.
Clam...bear...fish...frog...gribbet.
麦琪:是的,杰森,
Maggie: Yes Jason, you're right Jason,
说的对.我一定要把全医院的人都开除,杰森.
I'll make sure the whole hospital staff is fired Jason.
亲爱的,只要你打个电话,
Sweetheart if you let me get off the phone I'll come and get you.
我就来接你回家.是的,我们都等不及了.
Yes, we can't wait to have you home.
迈克:爸爸怎么样?还耍性子呢?
Mike: How's Dad?Still cranky?
麦琪:这么说吧,今天上午,医院里的那个活宝真让我头疼.对了,他让我问问你宴会准备的怎么样了.
Maggie: Let me put it this way, this morning the hospital Chaplin attacked him, by the way he wanted me to ask you how the plans for the banquet are coming.
迈克:啊,宴会?
Mike: Ah, the banquet?
麦琪:呃,嗯?
Maggie: Um hmm.
迈克:老实说吧,我还没遇到一个麻烦呢.
Mike: Well I can honestly say that not one problem has come to my attention.
麦琪:哦,他听了会很高兴的.
Maggie: Oh, he'll be glad to hear that.
迈克:哦,回头见.(吹口哨)本,卢克,集合.怎么回事?
Mike: Ok see you later.(Whistling sound) Ben, Luke, front centre.What's going on?
本:我在教卢克刮脸呢.
Ben: I'm teaching Luke how to shave.
迈克:本,过来.
Mike: Ben, come here.
本:怎么?噢!
Ben: What?Ouch!
迈克:卢克,别再让他拿着锋利的东西靠近你.
Mike: Luke, don't ever let him come near you with a sharp object again.
好吧,
Alright, now listen, Dad wants to know how things are coming along with
听着,爸爸想知道宴会的事安排的怎么样了.
the banquet.
卢克:哦,很好.一切都很顺利.
Luke: Uh, great, everything's great.
迈克:本?
Mike: Ben?
本:你听见了,很好.噢!好,
Ben: You heard him, great.Ouch!OK, fine, We haven't done anything.We...
好,我们什么还没干呢.我们…我们正要去呢,可他要刮脸,噢!
we'll going to, but he shaving come up.Ouch!
迈克:听着,别找借口了.你们俩去打电话.
Mike: Listen, no more excuse, You both get on that phone.
本:好的, 我问问场地布置和娱乐表演.你找那个餐厅的经理.
Ben: Ok fine, I'll call about the decorations and the entertainment, you call the catering manager.
卢克:那我说什么啊?
Luke: Well what do I say?
本:你知道…宴会的事.
Ben: You know...banquet stuff.
卢克:好,有个问题,什么是宴会?
Luke: Ok one question, what's a banquet?
本:就是活受罪,你穿着别人的衣服,
Ben: Living torture, you wear somebody else's clothes,
吃乏味的东西,听一些唠里唠叨的人站起来为死人吹牛皮.
eat cardboard food and some gas bag stands up and preaches about dead people.
卢克:听起来像周日晚上在厨房里的情景.你爸爸喜欢这套玩意儿?
Luke: Sounds like Sunday night at the soup kitchen, your dad likes this stuff?
本:没人喜欢,但这是惯例.
Ben: Nobody does but its tradition.
卢克:那既然没人喜欢,我们来点新鲜的东西怎么样?
Luke: Well if nobody likes it why don't we make a new tradition?
杰森:麦琪,请放手.我不是残疾人,我自己能做,噢,天啊.
Jason: Maggie cut it out please, I'm not an invalid, I can do this myself, oh boy.
麦琪:杰森,如果你非得去参加宴会,医生说不要工作,
Maggie: Jason if you wanna go to this banquet the doctor says no work,
不要紧张,不要乱走动,还要按时止疼药.
no stress, no unnecessary movement and take your pain medication.
杰森:麦琪,我不想用药来止疼,因为我根本就不疼,噢,
Jason: Maggie I'm not gonna dull my senses with pharmaceuticals because
天啊.只是个哈欠,迈克.
I'm just not in any pain, ooooh boy, that was a yawn.Mike.
迈克:什么,爸爸.
Mike: Yeah Dad.
杰森:宴会的事怎么样了?
Jason: How are the plans for the banquet going?
麦琪:哦,不,别这样.迈克快走.
Maggie: Oh no you don't, Mike get lost.
迈克:呃,我很想跟你聊一会,爸爸.
Mike: Uh, glad we had this time to chat Dad.
麦琪:杰森,如果你执意要去,唯一的办法就是躺在担架上去.好了,你该吃药了.
Maggie: Jason if you keep this up the only way you are gonna go to this banquet is on a stretcher; now take your pain pill.
杰森:不,不,不,麦琪,我…噢,天啊.
Jason: Nope, nope, nope Maggie, I'm, oh boy.
麦琪:你要干嘛?
Maggie: What are you doing?
杰森:我只是想打个电话,我至少可以打几个电话问问.
Jason: I'm just trying to get to the phone so I can at least make some business calls.
麦琪:不,不,不,你只能坐在那里静养,先生.
Maggie: Nope, nope, nope, you just sit there and heal mister.
杰森:噢…噢,天啊,噢,天啊,噢,噢,噢,噢.
Jason: Ooooooooooh, oh boy, oh boy, oh, oh, oh, oh.
开萝尔:真难过,爸爸一个人吃饭.
Carol: I feel so bad Dad's eating alone.
麦琪:好的.收拾一下盘子,我们到客厅里吃去.
Maggie: Ok, gather your plates, we're eating in the living room.
杰森:噢,天啊.噢,天啊.
Jason: Oh boy, oh, oh boy.
麦琪:亲爱的,我们不想让你老是一个人吃饭.
Maggie: Sweet heart, we didn't want you to eat all by yourself.
杰森:哦,你们太体贴了.
Jason: Oh that's very thoughtful.
克莉丝:妈妈,我能吃花生奶油三明治吗?
Chrissy: Mom can I have a peanut butter sandwich?
麦琪:开萝尔,你能再给她做份花生奶油三明治吗?
Maggie: Carol would you please make her another peanut butter sandwich.
开萝尔:妈妈,我5岁的时候要是死盯着一样东西吃,你肯定会拒绝的.
Carol: Mom when I was five years old and only wanted to eat one thing, you put your foot down.
麦琪:他们都是凤尾鱼,你是鱼饵.
Maggie: They were anchovies and you smelt like a bait stand.
开萝尔:妈妈.
Carol: Mom.
麦琪:别担心.我会在花生奶油里加维生素的.
Maggie: Don't worry I'll get a vitamin to mash into the peanut butter.
克莉丝:请做的鼓鼓的.
Chrissy: Chunky style please.
麦琪:哦,会做的鼓鼓的.
Maggie: Oh it'll be chunky all right.
杰森:迈克,宴会的事怎么样了?
Jason: Mike so what about the banquet?
迈克:呃,我要是跟你谈这个,妈妈会杀了我的,爸爸.
Mike: Um, Mom will kill me if I discuss that with you Dad.
杰森:我总会好的,迈克.
Jason: I'm gonna be well someday Mike.
迈克:啊,关于宴会,啊,宴会准备很顺利.
Mike: Ah, well about the banquet, it's, ah, it's going a-ok.
杰森:食物怎么样,钱够花吗?
Jason: How about the food, are you within budget?
迈克:哦,我们…我削减了预算.
Mike: Well we're, ah, I cut the budget.
杰森:真的??减了多少?
Jason: Really?By how much?
迈克:呃.减了…100…块.
Mike: Uh, by one... hundred... smackers.
卢克:老兄,你说的对.穿这衣服真是透不过气来.
Luke: Boy you were right you really can't breathe these things.
迈克:哇,哇,等等.卢克,你该把这些东西拿出去.
Mike: Wow, wow, hold a second.Luke, you're supposed to take these things out.
卢克:哦,那鞋子里的小纸团怎么办?
Luke: Oh, what about the little balls of paper in the shoes?
麦琪:杰森,你能吃片药吗?
Maggie: Jason, won't you please take a pill.
杰森:不需要.迈克,我给你说白了吧,我对今晚的宴会不打放心.
Jason: Don't need one, Mike I gotta hand it to you, I had some trepidations about this banquet tonight,
你也许会让我在同事或贝罗斯医生面前难堪的.但你干的不错.
you know, maybe that you'd embarrass me in front of my colleagues or Doctor Bellows, but you've really come through.
迈克:哈哈哈.
Mike: Ha, ha, ha.
杰森:"施里卡拉玛91"?
Jason: Shrinkarama 91?
迈克:这,啊,太有样了,对吧?
Mike: That's, ah, really something huh?
杰森:我讨厌这个.
Jason: I hate it.
迈克:这是本干的.
Mike: Something that Ben did.
杰森:迈克,我让你负责宴会的.
Jason: Mike I put you in charge of this banquet.
迈克:哦,爸爸,这只是,呃,呃,我不想让两个孩子没事干.这可是我们第一次组织这么大的活动.
Mike: Well Dad, it, uh, it, uh, I just couldn't leave the little kids outta it.I mean it was our first big event.
杰森:对不起,对不起,喂,我觉得你们,呃,一定是走错包房了.
Jason: Pardon me, pardon me, hello, I think you fellas, uh; you must be in the wrong ball room.
音乐人:不可能,这不是"施里卡拉玛91"吗?
Musician: Impossible Senor, shrinkarama 91 no?
杰森:哦,是的,不过,我是说…迈克,四重奏呢?
Jason: Well yes but no, I mean...., Mike, where is the String Quartet?
迈克:呃,本?
Mike: Uh, Ben?
本:嘿,这个更好,而且便宜一半呢.
Ben: Hey this is better and for half the price.
杰森:哦,抱歉,小伙子们.但这是墨西哥流浪音乐,不适合这个场合.
Jason: Huh, I'm sorry guys but Mariachi music, that's all wrong for this evening.
音乐人:不要紧,先生,就说"道斯霍姆布莱斯一路平安…你好,巴米茨瓦的猫!
Musician: No problem Senor, just say adios Dos Hombres...
哈瓦那给予者,哈瓦那给予者,哈瓦那…"
and shalom, Bar Mitzvah cats!Havana giver, Havana giver, Havana ...
杰森:伙计们,猫们,停下,噢,天啊;你们能不能演奏一些适合精神病医生听的?
Jason: Guys, Cats, listen up, oh boy; can you play something more appropriate for a room full of psychiatrists?
音乐人:哦,我想我有点晕;是的,我想我有点晕了…
Musicians: Well I think I'm going outta my head; yes I think I'm going outta my head....
杰森:哦,这是什么?我们打算上块菌煮牛肉吗,迈克?
Jason: Oh, what's this?We're supposed to be having veal with truffles, Mike?
迈克:哦,卢克?
Mike: Uh, Luke?
卢克:嘿,我查过了,块菌是长在猪身上的真菌.我让他们上真正的菜.
Luke: Hey I looked it up, a truffle is a fungus rooted up by a pig, I got us some real food.
杰森:怎么能让穿着晚礼服的人吃玉米炒排骨呢,迈克?
Jason: You can't eat ribs and corn on the cob in tuxedoes, Mike?
迈克:卢克!
Mike: Luke!
卢克:别着急,看看这个.
Luke: Way ahead of you, check this out.
没有快乐的猪也能对付一下,只是有些不协调罢了.
I almost got the ones with out the happy hog but they were kinda stuffy.
杰森:没人会戴围脖的,对把?噢,天啊.
Jason: Nobody gets these bibs right?Oh boy.
麦琪:杰森,把药吃了.
Maggie: Here Jason, take this pill.
杰森:麦琪,求你了.我不吃药;别拿我当孩子.
Jason: Maggie please, I will not take the pill; do not treat me like a child.
麦琪:如果我真的把你当孩子,我会把药掺到饭里不会让你知道的.
Maggie: If I were treating like a child I'd mash it into your food so you'd never know.
法蒂玛:请问,你是西沃医生吗?
Fatima: Excuse me are you Doctor Sever?
杰森:是我.
Jason: Yes.
法蒂玛:我是法蒂玛!
Fatima: I am Fatima!
杰森:迈克!
Jason: Mike!
迈克:是卢克干的.
Mike: It's Luke.
卢克:是本.
Luke: Ben.
本:你们不会连这个都受不了吧.
Ben: Don't tell me you guys have a problem with this.
杰森:你们仨跟我来.
Jason: You three follow me.
卢克:去干嘛,我们闯祸了吗?
Luke: What happens now, do we get spanked?
本:那要看发蒂玛的了.
Ben: Hopefully by Fatima.
麦琪:请加点土豆.
Maggie: Just potatoes on this plate please.
开萝尔:妈妈,你在干嘛?
Carol: Mom, what are you doing?
麦琪:我把你爸爸当作孩子.
Maggie: I am treating your father like a child.
杰森:求求你,能悄悄地离开这里吗?你们三个告诉我一定没有新花样了.
Jason: Could you just leave with out drawing any more attention please.I want you three to tell me there are no more surprises.
卢克:你都看见了.
Luke: You've seen it all.
本:是的,其他的很枯燥;你不会有兴趣的.
Ben: Yeah the rest will be so boring; it'll make your eyes cross.
杰森:噢,我实在没办法了,噢…哇…
Jason: Oh, that's all I ask.Oh...Wa....
卢克:我知道吃药让你很生气.说实话,你跟我一样不相信医生了吧.
Luke:I knew you were angrily take your pain pills.Told me the truth, you don't trust doctor any more I do.
杰森:你是这么看的吗,卢克?好吧,
Jason: That's the message give you, Luke?All right.
主意听着,这表明我是多么相信医生,好了吧?
Watch this, this is how much I do trust doctors, all right?
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,我又要了点土豆因为你只能吃这个.
Maggie: Oh honey I had them give you extra potatoes cause that's all you can eat.
杰森:哦,这太好,我已经饿坏了.
Jason: Well that is just fine because I am ravenous.
麦琪:我知道你现在好多了.
Maggie: Well I know somebody is feeling a lot better.
杰森:是的,确实如此.
Jason: Yeah I certainly am.
麦琪:知道为什么吗?
Maggie: And do you know why?
杰森:嗯,我吃了药.
Jason: Um hmm, I took a pill.
开萝尔:你怎么知道的?
Carol: How did you know?
杰森:我知道,因为我吃药的时候就在那里,半个小时前,我跟孩子们在一起.
Jason: I know because I was there when I took it, half an hour ago when I out for the boys.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:我感觉棒极了.
Jason: And I feel great.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我觉得有件事还是告诉你吧.
Maggie: Oh Jason, I think there's something I've gotta tell you.
音乐人:先生们,女士们,下面有请"施里卡拉玛91"的幕后组织者,杰森西沃医生.
Musician: Ladies and gentlemen, I now give you the man behind Shrinkarama 91, Doctor Jason Sever
杰森:谢谢大家.呃,
Jason: Thank you very much, uh,
各位好朋友和同事们,
good friends and colleagues can we have a light on Doctor Bellows' table
请把灯光照到贝罗斯医生的桌子上.呃,
please, and, uh, we are here tonight to honor a great man,
今晚我们要表彰一个伟人,是他让我们对身为精神病医生而感到骄傲.
a man who makes us all proud to be psychiatrists,
这个人是世界组名的,
he is a man known the world over as a brilliant therapist and a devout
杰出的临床专家和虔诚的学者.你们也许在猜他的头发是不是真的.
scholar and incase you're wandering no that's not his real hair.
开玩笑,当然了,这是玩笑.
I'm kidding, off course I'm kidding and Doctor Bellows has a great sense
另外,贝罗斯医生富有幽默感,看看他的妻子就知道了.
of humor, just look at his wife.
说到哪里了?哦,对,他是个伟人,是一个对我非常,非常,非常重要的人.呃,
Where was I, oh yes, he is a great man and, uh, a man who really, really, really means a lot to me, and uh, so the only way I can uh,
所以唯一的方式我可以,呃,
only way I can think of to properly express how I feel about uh,
我可以适当地表达我对,呃,你这位医疗界泰斗景仰之情就是,
this therapeutic nut bucket.
"你是我生命中的阳光,哦,是的,是的,这就是我为什么一直陪伴着你,当你,当你,当你,嘿,你是我的眼珠子,眼珠子,你永远在我的心里".我太喜欢阿尔费了,阿尔费也喜欢我.嘿,在座的有谁来自奥他州吗?
You are the sunshine in my life, oh yeah, oh yeah, that's why I'll always
stay around you, when you, when you, when you, hey, you are the apple of
my eye, eye, eye, eye, forever you stay in my heart.I'm just wild about
Alfy, Alfy's wild about me, hey.Anybody here from outta state
啊?奥他镇?奥他钱?哈哈哈.我知道,嘿,听好了,你们可以去拜访年迈的阿尔费贝罗斯医生.你们知道那种感情,对吗?
Huh?Outta town?Outta money?Ha, ha, ha, I know, hey well listen you can go in to see old Doctor Alfy Bellows, you know that feeling don't you?
你们还在等什么呢?阿尔费?1小时250分钟?开玩笑呢,这是值当的.哦,一张纸条:"你知道你在出自己的洋相吗?"
So what are you up to now Alfy?At two hundred and fifty an hour?I'm kidding, it's worth it.Oh, a note, "Do you know you're making a jackass of yourself?"
不,但我知道是怎么回事."伙计们打它.哦,鲨鱼,嘿,嘿,嘿,一条珍珠般干净的港湾,这让他们珍珠般的白净".大家一起唱.
No but I do know Mag the knife.Hit it boys.Oh the shark, hey
hey, hey, a pearly cheese bay, and it shows them pearly white, come on everybody
麦琪:杰森.
Jason: Well at jack night heads all the heave bay and he keeps it way outta site, oh Jenny darling, up, up, New York means a lot......(Continues singing).
杰森:(继续唱歌)
Maggie: Jason.
麦琪:杰森,杰森.
Maggie: Jason, Jason.
杰森:哦,我太难堪了.
Jason: Oh oh, I'm so embarrassed, I can't believe it.
真是难以置信.我忘了介绍自己的家人了.请把灯光转到这边里.
I forgot to introduce my family.Can I get a light please over here?
16号桌.我优秀的妻子-麦琪,
Table 16, my good wife Maggie, I love you,
16我爱你;我的儿子-迈克和本,还有我亲爱的女儿-开萝尔;我们的老朋友卢克在那边.呃,
my sons Mike and Ben and our darling daughter Carol,
16你们知道,当我看着这些漂亮的,
our old pal Luke over there and uh,
16富有朝气的,年轻的脸庞时,我就想,
you know I see all these beautiful fresh young faces and I think hey old
16嘿,阿尔费很快就要离开人世了.
Alf is gonna be dead soon.
现在快到尾声了,"着名的脸,最后的窗帘,你们的朋友,我们清楚,我们要把肯定的事全说出了".等等,再等一下.让我把铭文说完.(西班牙语)是的,我的大人物,他用自己的方式做了贡献.是的,老阿尔费贝罗斯.谢谢你,谢谢大家.阿尔费已经离开了.
And now the end is near, the famous face, the final curtains, your friends we make it clear we'll state our case of which we're certain, wait, wait, wait a second, let's give it up for my posy, my posy right here (speaks Spanish), yeah, my main man, he did it his way, yeah, old Alfy Bellows, thank you, thank you everyone, Alfy has left the building.
麦琪:哦,杰森,这全是我的错;我不该把药放到你的土豆里.
Maggie: Oh Jason it's all my fault; I never should have put that pill in your potatoes.
杰森:不,我不相信我在贝罗斯医生面前出丑了.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,贝罗斯医生是个专家.我相信他看的要深的多.我相信他不会看低你的.
00:22:27,700
Jason: No I can't believe I pulled that in front of Doctor Bellows. Maggie: Oh honey, Doctor Bellows is a professional I'm sure he's seen a lot worse.I'm sure he doesn't think any less of you.